[
  {
    "question": "What does Michael accuse Pam of stealing in the pilot of the first season?",
    "answers": [
      "Company's money",
      "Pens",
      "Post-it notes",
      "Michael's tie"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Michael Scott's middle name?",
    "answers": [
      "Andy",
      "Gary",
      "Kurt",
      "Evelyn"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Angela's cat killed by Dwight?",
    "answers": [
      "Ember",
      "Milky Way",
      "Petals",
      "Sprinkles"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the guy that Pam was engaged to before Jim?",
    "answers": [
      "Roy",
      "Glenn",
      "Ed",
      "Gabe"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the name of Jan's assistant at the corporate?",
    "answers": [
      "Todd",
      "Sadiq",
      "Vikram",
      "Hunter"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "How many minutes did Michael Scott work at the Scranton office?",
    "answers": [
      "66,924,540",
      "3,450,000",
      "9,986,000",
      "6,500,100"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Phyllis had a husband named Bob Vance who ran his own company. What do they sell?",
    "answers": [
      "Jukeboxes",
      "Microwaves",
      "Cars",
      "Refrigerators"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of facial hair does Stanley have?",
    "answers": [
      "Only a mustache",
      "Only a beard",
      "A mustache and a beard",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "If Michael had a gun with two bullets, he'd shoot Toby twice instead of who?",
    "answers": [
      "Hitler and Stalin",
      "Pol Pot and Hitler",
      "Mao Tse-Tung and Hitler",
      "Bin Laden and Hitler"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the title of Michael's movie?",
    "answers": [
      "Threat Over 9000",
      "Threat Over Midnight",
      "Threat Level Midnight",
      "Danger Level 9000"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the best dish that Kevin can cook?",
    "answers": [
      "Chili",
      "Tacos",
      "Spaghetti",
      "Chicken Soup"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What did Michael promised to give his Scott's Tots?",
    "answers": [
      "To pay for their tuition",
      "To pay for their cars",
      "To give them all apartments",
      "To give them a 10.000 dollars each"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  }
]